Women Against War; Records apap391
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Yahoo Group Correspondence, 2002-2021
  - OWN Women Against War Action, 2001
    - Celebrate the 60th Anniversary of the Cuban Revolution on Friday July 26, 7pm at FUUSA, 405 Washington Avenue, Albany., 2019 July 23
    - Save the date for the August 7th Showing of "The Nuns, The Pris, and The Bombs" 5:30 PM, at the Pine Hills Branch of the Albany Public Library, 2019 July 25
    - Where will they go? Demolishing Homes is a war crime! Contact the 2020 Presidential Candidates via Code Pink., 2019 July 26
    - 15th anniversary of arrs of Aref and Hossain--events planned for Sunday, August 4, 2019 July 27
    - WONDERFUL WOMEN and MEN TO SPEAK AND PERFORM on CLIMATE ISSUES, 2019 July 28
    - Spirit of the Suffragettes Presents Crys Matthews & Amy Rigby! Plus...Tuesday, July 30th 5 to 8 PM, Sanctuary for Independent Media, Troy, 2019 July 29
    - A reminder of some Capital District events to commemorate the 74th anniversaries of the bombings of Hiroshima and Nagasaki. Thursday, August 1st through Wednesday, August 7th., 2019 July 31
    - TO Those who care about PEACE AND JUSTICE AND PLANETARY SUSTAINABILITY and LUNCH, 2019 July 31
    - REMINDER: 15th anniversary of arrs of Aref and Hossain--events planned for Sunday, August 4, 2019 August 2
    - Volunteers needed for Sunday, August 4 For setup, 5 PM, serving food, 6 PM, Clean up: 6:30 PM until done, 2019 August 3
    - Fw: Spirit of the Suffragettes Presents Sammus & Nitty Scott. Tuesday, August 6th. 5 to 8 PM, Sanctuary for Independent Media, 2019 August 4
    - Remember Hiroshima & Nagasaki by Rallying for Peace. See rallies for peace in Yemen and other places led by Code Pink in NYC orattend if you can. New Code Pink Radio station. Listen weekly online., 2019 August 4
    - REMINDER: Wednesday, August 7th Showing of "The Nuns, The Pris, and The Bombs" Pine Hills branch of Albany Public Library, 5:30 PM, 2019 August 6
    - Register Today for Stand Against Racism: Immigrant Justice Advocacy Forum, 2019 August 7
    - Build on community to help the planet flourish: Commentary by Maureen Aumand, 2019 August 7
    - FW: "The River and the wall", August 22: revised poster/flier., 2019 August 7
    - Memorial Service for Barbara Spring to be held Saturday, September14, 2019, 4 PM at the Delmar Presbyterian Church, Delmar NY, 2019 August 8
    - Fw: Yemen prot on Friday in Albany, 2019 August 8
    - [Peace Action] Yemen prot on Friday TOMORROW in Albany at Senator Schumer's Albany Office, 1 Clinton Avenue at Noon., 2019 August 8
    - Full Memorial Minute for Barbara Spring, 2019 August 8
    - [upstatedroneaction] Sunday, August 11, SPECIAL: KB Plowshares7 - FACEBOOK Live & in DC ! 5 PM to 7 PM, 2019 August 9
    - Reminder: Capital Region PPC - Community Cookout Saturday, August 17th Noon to 3 PM Ridgefield Park, Albany. Plus canvasing and next meeting., 2019 August 10
    - TOO GOOD TO MISS:a Midsummer Dinner to Remember: from the KATERI Peace Conference- PLEASE SHARE, 2019 August 10
    - RAICES fundraiser, TONIGHT Tuesday. August 13 Fundraiser for RAICES, which works at the Texas border Great Flats Brewing, 6 PM to 8:30 PM, 2019 August 13
    - Film: "The River and The Wall" Thursday, August 22, 6:00 - 8:45 pm, Bethlehem Public Library, community room, 451 Delaware Ave., Delmar NY, 2019 August 15
    - Spirit of the Suffragettes P resents Tana Asili & Eljuri. Tuesday, August 20th 5-8 PM Sanctiary for Independent Media, 2019 August 17
    - Radio interview about "The River and the Wall"., 2019 August 17
    - Final Report GDAMS (Global Days of Action on Military Spending) 2019, 2019 August 20
    - Your Senator is in key position to promote peace by keeping these 19 good amendments in the FY 2020 NDAA reconciled bill, 2019 August 21
    - Fw: WAWaction Radio interview about "The River and the Wall"., 2019 August 24
    - Bus trip from the Capital District to the We the People March - September 21, 2019, 2019 August 24
    - Thank you! From Carrie Kuehl for all those people and organizations that helped make the showing of "The River and the Wall" and Aaron Mair'stalk such a success, 2019 August 26
    - WAWaction Thank you! From Carrie Kuehl for all those people and organizations that helped make the showing of "The River and the Wall" and Aaron Mair's talk such a success, 2019 August 26
    - Peace Action] Solidarity Labor Day Picnic and Celebration, Monday, September 2, 2019, Noon to 4:30 PM, Cook Park in Colonie, 2019 August 27
    - Free Dan Rather Tickets Going Fast, Friday September. 6th 7:30 PM at the SEFCU Arena. Free tickets required, see below., 2019 August 27
    - A surprise for Trump in France could be the start of Negotiations between Iran and the US and more effective attempts by the EU to ease the economic effects of US Sanctions., 2019 August 28
    - [Roundtable] YWCA - STAND AGAINST RACISM EVENT FOCUSING ON IMMIGRATION ISSUES - SEPT. 14th, 12;30 pm to 4:30 pm, SIENA COLLEGE, 2019 August 29
    - "Solidarity with Venezuela, End the Sanctions! US Hands off!" The James Connolly Forum, Thursday, September 5th, 7 PM, Oakwood Community Center, Troy NY, 2019 August 31
    - A beautifully done "torch song" about impeachment of the number 1Occupant, sung by Sandy Opatow of Emma's Revolution., 2019 August 31
    - Never Again Means Never Again. Stop the mass atrocities against immigrants. Sunday, September 8th, 2 PM, Taras Shevchenko Park, Troy NY, 2019 August 31
    - "The Age of Consequences" Tuesday, September 3rd. 7 PM to 8:45 PM, Bethlehem Public Library., 2019 September 1
    - Death and Resistance on the U.S.-Mexico Border: A Democracy Now! Special, 2019 September 2
    - Fw: UPCOMING ACTIONS: Calendar from Capital District Border Watch: From September 5th through September 13, 2019, 2019 September 3
    - Fwd: [CACN] Sept. 20 Student climate strike rally and marches Albany, 2019 September 4
    - Troy ACTION RE: Mayor Madden and the Edson Thevenin Killing. Thursday, September 5th at 6:15 pm, Troy City Hall, 2019 September 4
    - Fw: Part of an email from Peaceful Tomorrows, addressing the issue of Civilian Casualties suffered by US sold weapons in Yemen and Nigeria.Signed by many leading peace and civil rights organizations., 2019 September 5
    - Fw: [Keep Space for Peace Week - No to NATO Video, 2019 September 5
    - Art reception & show by Diane Reiner includes places of conflict "Faces and Places"Opening Reception Saturday, Sept. 7th 2-4 PM, Exhibit runs September 4th -30th, Niskayuna Public Library., 2019 September 6
    - REMINDER: Never Again Means Never Again - Sept 8, 2019, beginning at 2 pm in Tara Shevchenko Park, South Troy., 2019 September 6
    - STREET NAMING - VERA 'MIKE' MICHELSON WAY, Saturday, September 14th from 12:30 PM to 1 PM, Pennsylvania Avenue between Livingston Avenue and Beverly Avenue, Albany NY, 2019 September 8
    - Don't Miss the Albany Book Fival, Saturday, Sept. 14th !!! 10 am to 5 PM, U Albany Campus Center and an adjacent Big Tent., 2019 September 9
    - Interviewees sought for a documentary to honor and celebrate Rezsin Adams. Filming on September 21 and 28th, contact Cynthia Pooler of Focus on Albany., 2019 September 9
    - REMINDER: Thursday Sept 12 -- "Endings and Beginnings". Interfaith Story Circle, Thursday, September 12, 7 to 9 PM, First United Methodist Church of East Greenbush, 2019 September 9
    - Defund Hate Events This Week - Support Immigrants - no family separation - no ICE inhumane treatment, 2019 September 10
    - Join us: Defund Hate National Week o f Action; Albany, Latham & Glens Falls, 2019 September 11
    - Stop the Wars! Save the Planet! and more. New York City, September 20 through 23, 2019, 2019 September 12
    - REMINDER - Capital Region Poor People's Campaign Organizing Meeting: Monday, September 16, 6 PM at St. Vincent de Paul Church, Albany NY, 2019 September 13
    - Two Films: "Disturbing the Peace" Sept 17; "Vieques: An Unfinished Battle"; Sept. 28, 2019 September 15
    - Saratoga Peace Fair, Sunday, September 22, Noon to 4 PM, 24 Circular Street, Saratoga Springs NY, 2019 September 17
    - Reminder: Strike for the Climate, TOMORROW: Friday Sept 20, 2019, from 11am for "Time to Panic" March to Capital Park W Rally, starting at 1 PM, 2019 September 19
    - Fw: Spirit of the Suffragettes Grand Finale Presents KATANI andToko Telo. THIS Saturday 9/21, 3 pm to 6 PM at the Sanctuary for Independent Media, 2019 September 19
    - "Vieques: An Unfinished Battle" Saturday, September 28th 7:30 PM, First Unitarian Universalist Society of Albany, 405 Washington Avenue, 2019 September 23
    - James Yee, former army chaplain ministering to muslim detainees at Guantanamo to speak: Grafton Peace Pagoda 26th anniversary Ceremony, Saturday, Septeber 28th 11 am, 2019 September 23
    - THIS EVENING: Palinian Rights film "One Day in Gaza." Tuesday, September 24th, 6 PM, Pine Hills branch of the Albany Public Library, 517 Wern Avenue, Albany., 2019 September 24
    - Talking Openly About Race, Thursday, September 26th 4:15 PM craft talk, 7:30 PM Campus Center W Auditorium., 2019 September 24
    - Updated message about transportation to the Kashmir demonstrations in NYC when Indian Prime Minister Modi speaks, Friday September 27th. Busesleave at 7:30 am (boarding at 7 am Two locations, 2019 September 25
    - This Sunday, September 29th in NYC: Support the Kingsbay Plowshares 7, Holyrood Episcopal Church ~ Iglesia Santa Cruz, 2019 September 26
    - Donations of working sewing machines needed for project withrecently arrived refugees and immigrants. Meeting every week at RISSE., 2019 September 27
    - Important upcoming events. Monday, September 30th, Thursday, October 3rd, Monday, October 7th, 2019 September 29
    - Monday, October 14, 2019, 4:30 PM to 5:30 PM. Central Avenue andWolf Road, Colonie. Grannies for Peace Vigil honoring indigenous People's Day and working to stop the Climate Crisis., 2019 October 1
    - Friday Film: Young Scientists Saving the Planet, with director, Laura Nix. Friday, October 4th, 7 PM Page Hall, UAlbany downtown campus., 2019 October 2
    - Outstanding article written by Kate Cavanaugh, member of the WAW Iran Project and the Steering Committee, 2019 October 2
    - Fw: [unac] Prots during the UN General Assembly and upcomingevents, 2019 October 2
    - Bystander training, 2019 October 2
    - [CAAMI] Join Us! #HumanFirst Commitment Letter, 2019 October 3
    - NYS Peace Action to honor Bill McKibben. "Peace Action for the Earth" Monday, October 14th 7 to 9 PM, MIST Harlem, New York City, 2019 October 4
    - Please share this announcement: Witness at Tornillo movie screening, November 12., 2019 October 5
    - Fw: [bethlehem_for_peace] Keep space for peace vigil - in conjunction with events happening around the world. Monday, October 7th, 5PM to 6 PM, Four Corners intersection, Delmar NY, 2019 October 6
    - Women's Event with Ahmadiyya "Seeds for Peace" potluck and seed sorting and packing. Friday, October 11, 2019, 6 PM at Noor Mosque Schenectady NY, 2019 October 7
    - Meet Nikki Giovanni, Poet, Grandmother, Activist Thursday 10/10, at 7 PM, UAlbany Campus Center Ballroom, 1400 Washington Avenue, Albany, 2019 October 7
    - Alaa needs a used car to travel to classes at UAlbany. More details from Steve Downs in his email below, 2019 October 7
    - Will music stop the war in Yemen? A petition from Code Pink., 2019 October 8
    - Last call for Tour of Albany's 3 Anaerobic Digers -at the NorthWater Purification Plant - This Friday 10/11 @ 3 pm North Albany, 1 Canal Road South, 12204, 2019 October 8
    - Feisty Fridays plus A Minute a Day. to urge our Governor to declare a climate emergency for NY State., 2019 October 10
    - PRC screening of" Naila & the Uprising," Wednesday OCTOBER 16, 2019, 6:30PM, DELMAR REFORMED CHURCH, 386 DELAWARE AVE. DELMAR, 2019 October 10
    - Reminder: Grannies for Peace Indigenous People's Day vigil, Monday October 14, 4:30 to 5:30 PM Wolf Road and Central Avenue., 2019 October 10
    - Hi, Im Jane Fonda and let s do this! Weekly "Fire Dri ll Fridays" in Washington DC to focus on the Climate Cri sis and the Green New Deal and Connection between US mil itarism and climate change. Ideas for local involvement., 2019 October 11
    - More information about the Q&A after screening of" Naila & theUprising," Wednesday OCTOBER 16, 2019, 6:30PM, DELMAR REFORMED CHURCH, 386 DELAWARE AVE. DELMAR, 2019 October 13
    - Tommy Sands Peace Activist Bard on Sunday, 2019 October 15
    - [P@U]: 50 films from the Middle East North Africa at Key Auditorium, Siena College, this Fri-Sat, October 18th and 19th. Schedule on attached flyer., 2019 October 15
    - Unlikely Partners for Peace: Three presentations by Palinian activist and Zionist settler, 2019 October 17
    - Speakers and discussion about Extinction Rebellion in the CapitalDistrict and in the EU. Friday, October 25th 7 PM to 8:45 PM, Bethlehem Public Library., 2019 October 17
    - Save the dates: Two Showings of the documentary "Imprisoning a Generation." November 14th at Bethlehem Public Library and December 3rd at William K. Sanford Library, Loudonville NY, 2019 October 21
    - Trial Today! October 21st. Judge Limits Timony, Fival of Hope, 2019 October 21
    - Sierra Club Annual Dinner with Roger Downs speaking about the Climate Leadership & Community Protection Act: This Thursday 10/24/19 at 5:30 pm, Five Rivers Environmental Center, Delmar, 2019 October 22
    - Meet Sharon Olds & Ocean Vuong, Thursday. 10/24 U Albany Uptown Campus, 2019 October 22
    - REMINDER: Friday! 10/25/19, 7:00 pm, Extinction Rebellion & Climate Change Talk by Benjamin Wang & Pippa Bartolotti. Bethlehem Public Library, 2019 October 22
    - WOOC Podcast on situation in Syria, 2019 October 24
    - Annual Jim Perry Awards Tuesday, October 29th at 6 PM, B ull Moose Club, Albany - Che ck Out This Years Honorees!, 2019 October 24
    - Rakim, Hip hop artist and memoirist @UAlbany on Monday, October 28th. Free ! 7 PM UAlbany Performing Arts Center, 2019 October 26
    - Maud Easters current Waging Peace WAW blog, 2019 October 27
    - FW: INTERNATIONAL Symposium on Migrant Justice - Tuesday, 11/12/19, 5 PM to 9:30 PM in White Plains, Please share!, 2019 October 28
    - Sunday, November 3, 11:30 a.m.: "The River and the Wall" film-screening: Emmanuel Baptisit Church of Albany, 275 State Street., 2019 October 28
    - Violence against Native American women: "Just horrific"petition to Congress to support H.R. 3977. Details below., 2019 October 28
    - Please save the date, 2019 October 29
    - Limited number left! Get your tickets for "Witness at Tornillo" now. Tuesday, November 12, 2019, 7:30 to 9 PM, Landmark's Spectrum 8 theaters, Albany., 2019 October 30
    - FW: WAWaction Limited number left! Get your tickets for "Witness at Tornillo" now. Tuesday, November 12, 2019, 7:30 to 9 PM, Landmark's Spectrum 8 theaters, Albany., 2019 October 30
    - Fwd: November 14: NYC Metro Organizing for April 24-26 World Conference/Rally/March, 2019 October 30
    - Fall events begin this Friday and Sunday! At the Sanctuary for Independent Media., 2019 October 31
    - Renewable Energy & Sustainable Living Fair: Sat, Nov 16, 10-4, Armory at Sage College, 2019 November 2
    - Pakistani American Children's and YA Author, Aisha Saeed coming to Albany Public Library Wednesday, November 6th at 7 PM via the NYS Writer's Institute, 2019 November 3
    - Emergency Rally - Support Cuba Debate at United Nations This Wednesday 11/6, 5PM in Townsend Park, Albany, 2019 November 4
    - "Imprisoning A Generation"- 3 Documentary Screenings: Thursday,November 14th 7 PM in Delmar; Wednesday, November 20, 7 PM in Schenectady; Tuesday,December 3, 6:15 PM in Loudonville, 2019 November 4
    - Bselling Pakistani-American YA author, Wednesday November 6th, 7 PM, Albany Public Library, Main Branch. More details about the author and her visit to Albany., 2019 November 5
    - COST OF ENDLESS WAR TO BE ADDRESSED AT U ALBANY on NOV 20th 2:45 PM to 4 PM - ALL INVITED-Please share widely, 2019 November 5
    - A Forgotten Population: Incarcerated and formerly incarcerated Women, Tuesday, November 12th, 6-8 @ The Albany Barn, 2019 November 6
    - Pelosi: Commit to floor vote on Syria War Powers Resolution.Background and Petition., 2019 November 6
    - Ranked Ballot won with 73% in NYC Tuesday!, 2019 November 7
    - Veterans Day Parade November 11 - Reclaim Armistice Day Meet between 10:30 and 11:00 am on the southeast corner of Central Avenue and Partridge Street, 2019 November 7
    - Democracy Now! live streaming the 2019 presidential Forum on Environmental Justice in San Francisco CA beginning at 6 PM tonight,Friday, 11/8/19., 2019 November 8
    - CORRECTION: DN is streaming this forum from South Carolina StateUniversity ~ Democracy Now! live streaming the 2019 presidential Forum on Environmental Justice beginning at 6 PM tonight, Friday, 11/8/19., 2019 November 8
    - Peace Witness Conference at Powell House Nov 15-17 for Quakers and non-Quakers!, 2019 November 8
    - 24th Annual Tellabration "Mountains" Sunday November 17th at 3:30 PM at Proctors, Schenectady, 2019 November 9
    - Free Tickets Left! Why Diversity Fails, Tuesday, 11/12. PamelaNewkirk professor of journalism at NYU. 7:30 p.m. Conversation - Hearst Media Center, 645 Albany-Shaker Road, Colonie. Please register for the evening event!, 2019 November 10
    - Reminder of Wed Nov 13 Interfaith Story Circle - Stories ofGratitude New and Old, Association of Bosniaks, Watervliet NY, 7 to 9 PM Tour of the Mosque and Community Center at 6:45 PM, 2019 November 11
    - Something important you can do now (takes 1 minute) to reduce plastic in Albany County!, 2019 November 11
    - Nowhere to Go: New Barriers to Asylum & Refugee Crisis in Mexico, Mon, Nov 18, 7-9 PM, FUUSA, 2019 November 12
    - REMINDER: DOCUMENTARY: "Imprisoning a Generation" about four young Palinians - Thursday. November 14, Bethlehem Public Library, Delmar, 2019 November 12
    - This Saturday and next: special 2 day training workshop "The Battleof Big Ideas: A deep dive into Race, Class and Gender in NYS politics."Saturday, 11/16 and Saturday, 11/23, 10am to 4 PM, RSVP required., 2019 November 12
    - NYS Poor People's Campaign, Tuesday, Nov 19th, 7 PM All State Conference Call: Healthcare and Housing Organizing Training, 2019 November 13
    - Stephanie Savell speaks on the Costs of War: Next Nov 20, 2:45 PM, UAlbany, 2019 November 14
    - REMINDER: Green Energy Fair -This Saturday, November 16th, 10 am-4 pm, Sage College Armory on New Scotland Ave, 2019 November 14
    - Fw: concert of potential inter to you all, 2019 November 16
    - Fw: Reminder:" Nowhere to Go" - November 18th 7 to 9 PM at FUUSA 405 Wahington Avenue, Albany, 2019 November 17
    - Camino nuevo holiday Fundraiser, for Capital District Latinos Cultural Empowerment and Community Engagement Center. Warm clothing donations requed., 2019 November 18
    - ALBANY ALERT -- PLEASE CALL to stop massive tire burning, 2019 November 18
    - Sunday, November 24 at 4:30 PM - Public Discussion and Community Dinner - All are Welcome, The Fiqh and Dawah Center presents the first in aseries of Public Discussions about Islam, 2019 November 19
    - Reminder: UUP Event arranged by Women Against Wart: The Cost of War Project. Wednesday, November 29th from 2:45 to 4:95 PM in Biology 248UAlbany, 2019 November 19
    - Film: "The Beginning of the End of Nuclear Weapons": Saturday, Nov. 23, 7:30 PM, FUUSA, 405 Wahington Avenue, Albany, 2019 November 21
    - From Bethlehem Neighbors for Peace: Change in Monday vigil hours at the 4 Corners to 4 PM to 5 PM, 2019 November 22
    - REMINDER AND Personal Invitation from the speaker, Hesham El-Meligy to Sunday's Program and dinner at the Fiqh and Dawah Center on Sunday, November 24th from 4:30 to 7:30 PM, 2019 November 22
    - The bad bill is here in the Senate (about pretending to stop facial recognition.) Please contact your Senators and ban the use of facial recognition, 2019 November 25
    - Movie: "The infiltrators", Wednesday, December 4. at the Sanctuary for Independent Media. Filmmaker will speak at 4:30 PM, Potluck dinner at 6 PM and film showing at 7 PM, 2019 November 26
    - New! 2 Events with Salman Rushdie! Wednesday December 4th at 4:30 PM Registration required and limited seating. 7:30 PM event no registration requires., 2019 November 26
    - Fw: WAWaction New! 2 Events with Salman Rushdie! Wednesday December 4th at 4:30 PM Registration required and limited seating. 7:30 PM event no registration requires. [1 Attachment], 2019 November 27
- Yard Signs, 2006; 2015; Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Yard Signs and Billboards, 2006-2008 (Box 6, Folder 3)